Guide to the Walter Isard papers, 1938-1986.
Isard, Walter papers
- Ecologic Economic Book: Section 1.3 Dredging (Box 83, Folder 14b)
- Ecologic Economic Book: Chap. 3 (Box 83, Folder 14c)
- Ecologic Economic Book: Chap. 4 (Box 83, Folder 14d)
- Ecologic Economic: Chap. 5 (Box 83, Folder 14e)
- Appendix A (Box 83, Folder 14f)
- Appendix B (Box 83, Folder 14g)
- Ecologic-Economic Analysis for Reb. Dev. 1968: ESSA Project 1, 1968 (Box 83, Folder 15)
- ESSA Project 2 (Box 83, Folder 16)
- ESSA Project 3 (Box 83, Folder 17)
- Mss. Draft (Box 83, Folder 18)
- Bibliography (Box 83, Folder 19)
- WRSA Meeting, Newport Beach, Calif.--Feb. 1969 (Box 83, Folder 20)
- Chapter 1, Section 1.1; Economic Models for Regional Analysis (Box 83, Folder 21)
- Masters 1.2 (Box 83, Folder 22)
- Section 1.3 (Box 83, Folder 23)
- Section 1.4 (Box 83, Folder 24)
- Section 1.5 (Box 83, Folder 25)
- Section 2.1/2.2/2.3/2.4, 1968 (Box 83, Folder 26)
- Section 2.5 (Box 83, Folder 27)
- Section 2.6 (Box 83, Folder 28)
- Chapter 3 Completed (Box 83, Folder 29)
- Section 4.1 Typed Masters (Box 83, Folder 30)
- Section 4.2 Masters (Box 83, Folder 31)
- Section 4.3 (Box 83, Folder 32)
- Section 4.4 (Box 83, Folder 33)
- Section 4.5 (Box 83, Folder 34)
- Section 4.6 (Box 83, Folder 35)
- Section 4.7 (Box 83, Folder 36)
- Section 4.8 (Box 83, Folder 37)
- Section 4.9 (Box 83, Folder 38)
- Section 4.10 (Box 83, Folder 39)
- Section 4.11 (Box 83, Folder 40)
- Chapter 5 (Box 83, Folder 41)
- Ecologic-Economic Analysis for Regional Development (Box 83, Folder Item 42)
  Manuscript
- WAAS Correspondence 1967-1970, 1974-1976 (Box 84, Folder 1)
- Correspondence WAAS 1977 (Box 84, Folder 2)
- WAAS Correspondence 1978-1980 (Box 84, Folder 3)
- WAAS Correspondence 1981-1983, undated (Box 84, Folder 4)
- WU Correspondence 1974 (Box 84, Folder 5)
- Stuart Mudd File 1970: Hugo Boyko, WAAS, 1970-1971 (Box 84, Folder 6)
- WAAS Statutes/bylaws (Box 84, Folder 7)
- WAAS Mtg. Notes/Agendas/Minutes 1967-1981, 1967-1981 (Box 84, Folder 8)
- Curriculum Vitae--WAAS membership, 1974-1980 (Box 84, Folder 9a)
- Vita: Funck (Box 84, Folder 9b)
- WAAS Conferences 1960s-1990s, 1966-1994 (Box 84, Folder 10)
- WAAS Reports 1965-80, 1965-1980 (Box 84, Folder 11)
- WU, UNU Documents Misc., 1973-1979 (Box 84, Folder 12)
- WAAS Finances, 1975-1980 (Box 84, Folder 13)
- Newsletters WAAS/WU, Directory of Fellows, Publications, 1968-1991 (Box 84, Folder 14)
- World University--WAAS Misc. (Box 84, Folder 15)
- Misc. Publications (Box 84, Folder 16)
- Study--A Report on Steel and Related Industrial and Population Growth, 1952 (Box 85, Folder Item 1)
- Future Communities: One Alternative, 1968 (Box 85, Folder Item 2)
- 12th Urban Design Conference--New Communities: One Alternative Proceedings, 1968 (Box 85, Folder Item 3)
- New Communities: One Alternative, 1968 (Box 85, Folder Item 4)
- New Communities: One Alternative Vol.1 (Box 85, Folder Item 5)
- Ecologic-Economic Analysis for Regional Development Report, 1968 (Box 85, Folder Item 6)
- Rotterdam WU 1984 Regional Science, 1982-1984 (Box 85, Folder Item 7)
- Regional Impacts of U.S.-Mexico Economic Relations (Box 86, Folder 1)
- RSA Mexico Conference 1981 Paper: Managing Conflict Among Border & Other Impacted Regions, 1980-1982 (Box 86, Folder 2)
- Roger Fisher Interaction (Harvard 1979-80), 1, 1979 (Box 86, Folder 3)
- Roger Fisher Interaction 1979-1980, 2, 1979 (Box 86, Folder 4)
- Roger Fisher Interaction 1979-1980, Papers cont.,3, 1979 (Box 86, Folder 5)
- University of Illinois--Peace Science Notes, articles, and reports on steel (1984-1985), 1984-1985 (Box 86, Folder 6)
- University of Illinois--Peace Science Program Proposals, Papers/ Misc. (1984-1985), 1984-1985 (Box 86, Folder 7)
- University of Illinois--Peace Science Budgets, Peace Science Fund, Course offerings (1984-1985), 1984-1985 (Box 86, Folder 8)
- Funding/Correspondence 1980-1982, 1980-1982 (Box 86, Folder 9)
- Cornell Peace Studies Fundraising (1981-6), 1981-1982 (Box 86, Folder 10)
- Cornell Peace Studies faculty meetings, proposals, budgets (1981-6), 1981-1990 (Box 86, Folder 11)
- Cornell Peace Studies Correspondence, Faculty lists (1981-1986), 1981-1986 (Box 86, Folder 12)
- Moore-McCormach, 1981 (Box 86, Folder 13a)
- Cornell Peace Science Studies Notes, Misc. Publications (1981-1986), 1981-1986 (Box 86, Folder 13b)
- Misc. (Box 86, Folder 14)
- Notes on Casual History 1982, JPS Article 1, 1982 (Box 86, Folder 15)
- Notes on Casual History 1982, 2, 1982 (Box 86, Folder 16)
- WI's Definition of Peace Science Manuscript (original), 1 (Box 86, Folder 17)
- WI's Definition of Peace Science Manuscript (original), 2 (Box 86, Folder 18)
- World University--News Bulletins 1981-6, 1981-1986 (Box 87, Folder 1)
- PSSI Newsletters--Jan 1977-Jan 1987, 1977-1987 (Box 87, Folder 2)
- PSSI Tentative Programs--N. American & European Conferences, Aug. 1977- Aug. 1990, 1977-1990 (Box 87, Folder 3)
- RSA Conferences/Misc., 1979-1986 (Box 87, Folder 4)
- RSA Newsletters--May 1971-Jan 1987, 1971-1987 (Box 87, Folder 5)
- RS Papers--IRSR Correspondence, 1978-1986 (Box 87, Folder 6)
- RS Papers--IRSR Guidelines, Cornell Archive, 1980-1984 (Box 87, Folder 7)
- RS Meetings--Council/Business, Membership Info., Reports, Proposals, 1979-1986 (Box 87, Folder 8)
- RSA Correspondence 1978-1982, 1978-1982 (Box 87, Folder 9)
- RSA Correspondence 1983-1986, 1983-1986 (Box 87, Folder 10)
- Ballinger Press--Correspondence 1981-1984, 1981-1984 (Box 87, Folder 11)
- Ballinger Press--Royalty Statements, Announcements, Notes (Box 87, Folder 12)
- RSUE--North Holland Correspondence, 1979-1986 (Box 87, Folder 13)
- RSUE--North Holland, Papers, Subscribers, Royalties, Announcements, Notes (Box 87, Folder 14)
- Publisher Correspondence--Allen &Unwin, Free Press, MIT, Sage, Blackwell, Johns Hopkins (Box 87, Folder 15)
- Venezuela-April 1982, S. Korea Visit--Aug. 1983, 23rd European RSA, Potiers--Aug. 1983, N. American PSSI 19, Urbana, Nov. 1983, ASSA/AEA, San Francisco--Sept. 1983, UMEA 1983, 1982-1983 (Box 88, Folder 1)
- Tokyo Conferences--Aug. 1983, WU Congress 15-16 Aug. 1983, RS Pacific Conference, 5th Tokyo Transport Conference, 1979-1983 (Box 88, Folder 2)
- International Conference on Urban Growth &Economic Development--Taipei, Taiwan--9-14 January 1984, 1983-1984 (Box 88, Folder 3)
- ISA, Atlanta--March 1984; 2nd WU Conf., Rotterdam, June 1984; 15th Pittsburgh on Modeling & Simulation--April 1984, 1982-1984 (Box 88, Folder 4)
- AAG, Washington, D.C.--April 1984; APSA, Washington, D.C.--Sept. 1984; ISA (PSSI) Wash. D.C.--March 1985; Scientific Geography Commission, Athens, GA--March 1985; AAG, Detroit--April 1985, 1983-1984 (Box 88, Folder 5)
- ASSA 1984 Annual Mtg. Dallas--Dec. 28-30; SE RSA 1984; RSA Malaysia 1984, 1984 (Box 88, Folder 6)
- Korea-U.S. Joint Seminar on Urban/Regional/Transportation Development Planning & Environmental Management--Aug. 18-24, 1985, 1984-1985 (Box 88, Folder 7)
- WU International Workshop, Innovation Technological Change and Spatial Impacts--Melbourne, Australia 21-24 Aug. 1985, 1984-1985 (Box 88, Folder 8)
- PSSI 19TH/20th European Conference: Programs, correspondence, papers--Sept. 1, 1985, 1982-1985 (Box 88, Folder 9)
- RSA--Hawaii, Aug. 1985; RSA 25th European Congress, Budapest--Aug. 1985; IEA, Stockholm--Oct. 1985; ASSA, AEA, PSSI, NYC--Dec. 1985, 1985 (Box 88, Folder 10)
- 21st N. America. PSSI, U.Maryland--Nov. 1985; AAG, Minneapolis--May 1986; WU/PSSI, Tokyo--Aug. 1986, 1985-1986 (Box 88, Folder 11)
- 26th RSA European, Krakow--Aug. 1986; EEA, Vienna--Aug. 1986, 21st. European, Amsterdam--Aug. 1986, 1986 (Box 88, Folder 12)
- 22nd N. American PS Conf., Detroit--Nov. 1986; RSA Ohio St.--33rd N. American mtgs., Columbus--Nov. 1986; AEA (ASSA) New Orleans--Dec. 1986, 1986 (Box 88, Folder 13)
- Article Reprints, 1942-1951 (Box 89, Folder 1)
  Isard articles
- Article Reprints/Manuscripts, 1952-1957 (Box 89, Folder 2)
- Article Reprints/Manuscripts, 1958-1962 (Box 89, Folder 3)
- Article Reprints/Manuscripts, 1961-1965 (Box 89, Folder 4)
- Article Reprints/Manuscripts, 1966-1968 (Box 89, Folder 5)
- Article Reprints/Manuscripts, 1969-1971 (Box 89, Folder 6)
- Article Reprints/Manuscripts, 1971-1973 (Box 89, Folder 7)
- Article Reprints/Manuscripts, 1973-1977 (Box 89, Folder 8)
- Article Reprints/Manuscripts, 1978-1980 (Box 89, Folder 9)
- Article Reprints/Manuscripts, 1981-1983 (Box 89, Folder 10)
- Article Reprints/Manuscripts, 1983-1984 (Box 89, Folder 11)
- Misc. Article reprints, manuscripts, drafts, 1962-1984 (Box 89, Folder 12)
- Misc. Article reprints, manuscripts, drafts, 1965-1990 (Box 89, Folder 13)
- Procedural documents: Journal of Peace Science [manuscript submission/processing/editing, form letters]; World university membership guidelines, tax and financial documents, 1979 (Box 90, Folder 1)
- Journal of Peace Science/Conflict Management and Peace Science correspondence/rejections/requests for revision, 1984-1986 (Box 90, Folder 2)
- Old proposals: Economic Development Agency; NSF Zinc; Public Health: air quality, 1968-1983 (Box 90, Folder 3)
- Dynamics of Spatial Interaction and Optimal Space-time development [1], 1979 (Box 90, Folder 4)
- Dynamics of Spatial Interaction and Optimal Space-time development [2], 1979 (Box 90, Folder 5)
- CORNELL (+Upenn) Misc. Peace Science Project., 1976-1978 (Box 90, Folder 6)
- TEACHING MATERIALS and notes on Intro to Regional Science (Book), 1967-1982 (Box 90, Folder 7)
- Bergson and WI on social welfare--conflict analysis, 1971 (Box 90, Folder 8)
- Old General Theory, Social Decision Rule, book materials, 1968 (Box 90, Folder 9)
- Manuscript [1] General Equilibrium Theory, Approx 1960's (Box 90, Folder 10)
- Manuscript [2] General Equilibrium Thoery, Approx 1960's (Box 90, Folder 11)
- Manuscript [3] General Equilibrium Theory, Approx 1960's (Box 90, Folder 12)
- Peace Science Fundraising (A-D), 1961-1982 (Box 90, Folder 13)
- Peace Science Fundraising (E-H), 1981-1982 (Box 90, Folder 14)
- Peace Science Fundraising (J-L), 1980-1983 (Box 90, Folder 15)
- Peace Science Fundraising (L-M), 1979-1982 (Box 90, Folder 16)
- Peace Science Fundraising (N-S), 1981-1982 (Box 90, Folder 17)
- Peace Science Fundraising (Spector-Williams), 1978-1984 (Box 91, Folder 1)
- Venezuela project proposal., 1982 (Box 91, Folder 2)
- University Appointments/projects/fundraising; Cornell, Harvard, Umaryland, 1967-1984 (Box 91, Folder 3)
- Cornell Econ appointment/ Upenn Regional Science appointment, 1978-1991 (Box 91, Folder 4)
- Student materials: Arroyo-Aziz, 1981-1983 (Box 91, Folder 5)
- Student Materials: Bruce Burton, 1983-1984 (Box 91, Folder 6)
- Student Materials: Stan Czamanski, 1981-1983 (Box 91, Folder 7)
- Student Materials: Anselin-Johnson, 1978-1989 (Box 91, Folder 8)
- Student Materials: Kai Michaelis, PhD, 1981-1982 (Box 91, Folder 9)
- Student Materials: Koeppel-de Luca, 1980-1983 (Box 91, Folder 10)
- Student Materials: Virginia Maclaren, 1980-1982 (Box 91, Folder 11)
- Student Materials: Katsumi Nishina, 1981-1982 (Box 91, Folder 12)
- Student Materials: Katsumi Nishina, 1981-1984 (Box 91, Folder 13)
- Student Materials: Marcus-Seim, 1980-1986 (Box 91, Folder 14)
- Student Materials: Christine Smith, 1980-1984 (Box 91, Folder 15)
- Student Materials: Sparrow-Williams, 1981-1985 (Box 91, Folder 16)
- Student materials: Wood-Yamazaki, 1983-1984 (Box 91, Folder 17)
- Rotterdam Congress / Econ Courses, 1990; 1978-9 (Box 92, Folder 1)
- Conference Papers, 1979-1983 (Box 92, Folder 2)
- November RSA Chicago Conference, 1983 (Box 92, Folder 3)
- Conference Papers, 1984 (Box 92, Folder 4)
- Jan. Taiwan Paper, 1984 (Box 92, Folder 5)
- Klaasen Volume Papers, 1984 (Box 92, Folder 6)
- Geography of Arms Manufacture: Paper w/ Anderton, 1984 (Box 92, Folder 7)
- WU Rotterdam June Paper, 1984 (Box 92, Folder 8)
- AEA Dallas Paper, 1984 (Box 92, Folder 9)
- Conference Papers, 1985 (Box 92, Folder 10)
- Nov. RSA (U.Penn) Correspondence, 1985 (Box 92, Folder 11)
- Conference Papers, 1986 (Box 92, Folder 12)
- CMPS Paper Vol7,18,6,1,2 (Box 92, Folder 13)
- Cornell Peace Science (establishment of), 1980-1981 (Box 92, Folder 14)
- Cornell Peace Studies Program, 1975-1984 (Box 92, Folder 15)
- Cornell Peace Studies Program (Correspondence/funding), 1978-1983 (Box 92, Folder 16)
- PS Institute Cornell, 1980-1981 (Box 92, Folder 17)
- Drafts: PS Institute Proposal, 1980 (Box 92, Folder 18)
- Cornell PS Major Proposal, 1981-1982 (Box 92, Folder 19)
- Cornell PS Major Proposal, 1981-1982 (Box 92, Folder 20)
- Cornell Peace Studies / Peace Science: Program proposals / developments, 1978-1984 (Box 93, Folder 1)
- Cornell Peace Studies / Peace Science: Correspondence, notes, reports., 1977-1983 (Box 93, Folder 2)
- Cornell Peace Science Institute: (est. 1981) Correspondence, newsletters, etc., 1980-1981 (Box 93, Folder 3)
- CVs--misc., 1979-1981 (Box 93, Folder 4)
- Isard/Maclaren Paper, 1979/1980 (Box 93, Folder 5)
- Notes / Papers [RSA], 1975-1977 (Box 93, Folder 6)
- Notes/ Papers [PSSI], 1970-1982 (Box 93, Folder 7)
- Notes / Papers [PRSI], 1970-1971 (Box 93, Folder 8)
- Notes / Papers [RSA], 1970-1971 (Box 93, Folder 9)
- Notes / Papers [RSA], 1972-1974 (Box 93, Folder 10)
- Notes / papers [RSA], 1982-1983 (Box 93, Folder 11)
- WU Notes and Papers, 1977-1983 (Box 93, Folder 12)
- Misc. 1, 1968-1982 (Box 93, Folder 13)
  lectures, seminars
- Misc. 2, 1983 (Box 93, Folder 14)
  Rotterdam papers and Political Geography notes
- Misc. 3, 1983 (Box 93, Folder 15)
  Forum Article May 1983; UMEA R&D Paper June 1983
- Michigan Lecture, 1963 (Box 94, Folder 1)
  "Impact of Military Cutbacks"
- Karlsruhe paper, 1979 (Box 94, Folder 2)
  "Desireable Properties of Social Decision Procedures and Social Rationality"
- Alonso, Anselin, Isard, 1980 (Box 94, Folder 3)
  "General Political Equilibrium"
- Cambridge Mass. WU/PSSI mtg. Paper w/ C Smith., 1980 (Box 94, Folder 4)
  "Characteristics of Conflict Management Procedures"
- Munich RSSA-PSSI, 1980 (Box 94, Folder 5)
- Cornell PSSI Seminar, 1981 (Box 94, Folder 6)
- Guanajuato paper w/ C. Smith., 1981 (Box 94, Folder 7)
  "Managing Conflicts among Border and Other Impacted Regions"
- UMEA Paper, 1981 (Box 94, Folder 8)
  "Incorporation of Conflict and Policy Analysis in an Integrated Multiregion Model" Contains Revision. June UMEA.
- UMEA conference summary remarks, 1981 (Box 94, Folder 9)
- 4th Tokyo Transport conference; paper w./ C. Smith., 1981 (Box 94, Folder 10)
  "Toward a More Scientific Approach to Conflict Management in Transportation and Other Areas" Prepared for August conference. Contains summary paper.
- Barcelona RSA - Notes on Regionalism, 1981 (Box 94, Folder 11)
- Geneva PSSI - Transparencies, 1981 (Box 94, Folder 12)
- Austrailia - Energy notes & paper, 1981 (Box 94, Folder 13)
- Philadelphia PSSI paper & summary Remarks, 1981 (Box 94, Folder 14)
- October RSA Paper, 1981 (Box 94, Folder 15)
  "Linked Integrated Multi-region Models at the International Level"
- Montreal RSA, 1981 (Box 94, Folder 16)
- w/ C. Smith "Linked Integrated Multiregion Models at the International Level, 1983 (Box 94, Folder 17)
- Cincinnati ISA-PSSI paper, 1982 (Box 94, Folder 18)
- Binghamton - NE PS conference paper, 1982 (Box 94, Folder 19)
- Arlie House Paper/presentations notes. w/ C. Smith., 1982 (Box 94, Folder 20)
- A Dynamical Systems Approach to Learning Processes in Conflict Mediation, 1982 (Box 94, Folder 21)
- Policy Space Analysis w/ C. Smith, 1981-1983 (Box 94, Folder 22)
- w/ C. Smith "Elementary Locational Analysis in Policy Space", 1981-1983 (Box 94, Folder 23)
- w/ C. Smith "Matching Conflict Situation and Conflict Management Procedures", 1981 (Box 94, Folder 24)
- HU Architecture course lectures, with Tzonis, 1969-1970 (Box 95, Folder 1)
- Location theory lectures (Box 95, Folder 2)
- Intro to Regional Science lectures, 1971 (Box 95, Folder 3)
- Intro to Regional Science lectures, 1971 (Box 95, Folder 4)
- Old Location Theory lectures, 1950-1951 (Box 95, Folder 5)
- Old Location Theory lectures, 1950-1951 (Box 95, Folder 6)
- Location Theory, 1966 (Box 95, Folder 7)
- Location Theory lectures, Harvard, 1949-1950 (Box 95, Folder 8)
- Location Theory lectures, Cornell, 1979-1980 (Box 95, Folder 9)
- Advanced Social Science lectures, Cornell, 1982-1983 (Box 95, Folder 10)
- Preface and Postscript (Box 95, Folder 11)
- Chapters 2, 3 and 4 (Box 95, Folder 12)
- Chapters 5 and 6 (Box 95, Folder 13)
- Chapters 11 and 12 (Box 95, Folder 14)
- Chapters 13 and 14 (Box 95, Folder 15)
- Lectures, chapters, miscellaneous (Box 95, Folder 16)
- Lectures, 1971 (Box 95, Folder 17)
- Lectures, 1971 (Box 95, Folder 18)
- Notes, miscellaneous (Box 95, Folder 19)
- Location Theory lectures, 1950-1982 (Box 96, Folder 1)
- Location Theory (Box 96, Folder 2)
- Political Geography Paper, unpublished, 1985 (Box 96, Folder 3)
- Conflict Management and Peace Science research group (Box 96, Folder 4)
- Illinois Honorary Degree (Box 96, Folder 5)
- Information study, 1985-1989 (Box 96, Folder 6)
- Miscellaneous Research (Box 96, Folder 7)
- Peace Science, U Penn and Cornell, 1980s (Box 96, Folder 8)
- Peace Science, U Penn and Cornell, 1980s (Box 96, Folder 9)
- Correspondence on RSA Europe, 1964-1967 (Box 96, Folder 10)
- Miscellaneous RSA/PS Europe, 1960s (Box 96, Folder 11)
- Correspondence re: grad group U Penn, 1980s (Box 96, Folder 12)
- General Theory, miscellaneous paper (Box 96, Folder 13)
- Cornell ideas, 1970s (Box 96, Folder 14)
- Levine and Rouse, Harlem project (Box 96, Folder 15)
- WAAS Roiterdam, Tokyo, 1984, 1986 (Box 96, Folder 16)
- Isard/Burton, NYC as a World Capital, 1983 (Box 96, Folder 17)
- Miscellaneous papers (Box 96, Folder 18)
- Miscellaneous papers (Box 96, Folder 19)
- First International Congress of A and S (Box 96, Folder 20)
- Correspondence, 1980s (Box 96, Folder 21)
- Work w/ Panagis Liossatos on Spatial Dynamics (Box 97, Folder 1)
- Notes on the Dynamic Description of Systems, 1976 (Box 97, Folder 2)
- Notes for Class, 1971 (Box 97, Folder 3)
- Notes for Class, Dec 1971-May 1972 (Box 97, Folder 4)
- Notes for Class, 1971-1972 (Box 97, Folder 5)
- Notes: Location Theory and Gravitational Interaction", 1971-1972 (Box 97, Folder 6)
- Notes for Class, 1971-1972 (Box 97, Folder 7)
- Notes for Class, 1971-1972 (Box 97, Folder 8)
- Notes for Class, Sep. Oct. 1970 (Box 97, Folder 9)
- Notes for Class, Oct. 1970 (Box 97, Folder 10)
- Notes: on Non-parametric Satatistics - Peace Science (Box 97, Folder 11)
- Notes for "Quantitative Methods in Conflict Analysis, 1977-1979 (Box 97, Folder 12)
- Quantitative Methods in Conflict Analysis, 1977-1979 (Box 97, Folder 13)
- Quantitative Methods in Conflict Analysis, 1977-1979 (Box 97, Folder 14)
- Notes on System Evolution, 1976-1974 (Box 98, Folder 1)
- Notes on Evolution of Cities, 1974 (Box 98, Folder 2)
- Isard and Leozardis notes, 1978-1974 (Box 98, Folder 3)
- Notes, 1975-1972 (Box 98, Folder 4)
- Transport Investment and Optimal Space-Time Development, 1973 (Box 98, Folder 5)
- Isard and Kanemoto, 1976 (Box 98, Folder 6)
- Notes, 1977 (Box 98, Folder 7)
- Isard & Liossatos, 1974-1972 (Box 98, Folder 9)
- Isard & Kanemoto, 1972-1975 (Box 98, Folder 10)
- Isard and Liossatos, 1975-1972 (Box 98, Folder 11)
- Isard & Liossatos, 1975-1972 (Box 98, Folder 12)
- Isard & Liossatos, 1974 (Box 98, Folder 13)
- Isard & Liossatos, 1974 (Box 98, Folder 14)
- Isard & Liossatos, 1973-1972 (Box 98, Folder 15)
- Umodel with Consumption Tax and variable transport rate, 1973 (Box 98, Folder 16)
- Isard & Liossatos, 1972-1974 (Box 98, Folder 17)
- Isard & Liossatos, 1971-1972 (Box 99, Folder 1)
- Isard & Liossatos, 1971-1972 (Box 99, Folder 2)
- Isard & Liossatos, 1971 (Box 99, Folder 3)
- Isard & Liossatos, 1971 (Box 99, Folder 4)
- Isard & Liossatos, 1971 (Box 99, Folder 5)
- Isard & Liossatos, 1971 (Box 99, Folder 6)
- Isard & Liossatos, 1971 (Box 99, Folder 7)
- Isard & Liossatos, 1971-1973 (Box 99, Folder 8)
- Appendix to "Social Energy..."; K.J. Arrow Paper; Isard Draft; Jutila Paper, 1972-1973 (Box 99, Folder 9)
- Jutila paper; Isard and Kaniss paper, misc. notes, 1972-1978 (Box 99, Folder 10)
- Isard & Liossatos, 1976 (Box 99, Folder 11)
- Isard Drafts, undated (Box 99, Folder 12)
- Adler-Karlsson paper + Misc. notes (w/ Liossatos), 1973 (Box 99, Folder 13)
- Regional Dynamics (Liossatos), 1972 (Box 99, Folder 14)
- Isard & Liossatos, 1973 (Box 99, Folder 15)
- Pollution models, 1972 (Box 99, Folder 16)
- Drafts to be typed, 1973 (Box 99, Folder 17)
- Isard & Liossatos: full drafts, undated (Box 99, Folder 18)
- Correspondence, 1986-1994 (Box 100, Folder 1)
- MIRD Coefficient for BNL Interregional I-O, undated (Box 100, Folder 2)
- Harvard RS Group, 1967-1971 (Box 100, Folder 3)
- Misc. RS & PS brochures, advertisements, etc, 1979 (Box 100, Folder 4)
- US Information about WI (FBI/CIA), 1942-1986 (Box 100, Folder 5)
- Misc. Reasearch, 1980-1990 (Box 100, Folder 6)
- Misc. Reasearch, 1980-1990 (Box 100, Folder 7)
- Arms control materials, 1985 (Box 100, Folder 8)
- Arms control materials, 1985 (Box 100, Folder 9)
- misc. Correspondence, 1980-1981 (Box 100, Folder 10)
- List of articles and their names (Box 101, Folder 1)
  Isard's CV
- Article 1 - Transport Development & Building, 1942 (Box 101, Folder 2)
- Article 2 - A Neglected Cycle: The Transport Building Cycle, 1942 (Box 101, Folder 3)
- Article 3 - The Transport Building Cycle in Urban Development, 1943 (Box 101, Folder 4)
- Article 4 - Economic Implications of Aircraft, 1945 (Box 101, Folder 5)
- Article 6 - The Atom and the Economy, 1947-1948 (Box 101, Folder 6)
- Article 7 - Some Economic Implications of Atomic Energy, 1948 (Box 101, Folder 7)
- Article 8 - Some Locational Factors in the Iron and Steel Industry Since the Early Nineteenth Century, 1948 (Box 101, Folder 8)
- Article 9 - Metropolitan Site Selection, 1949 (Box 101, Folder 9)
- Article 10 - Atomic Power Politics, 1949 (Box 101, Folder 10)
- Article 11 - Atomic Power and Economic Development, 1949 (Box 101, Folder 11)
- Article 12 - The Futue Locational Pattern of Iron and Steel Production in the U.S., 1949 (Box 101, Folder 12)
- Article 13 - Interregional Variations in Economic Fluctuations, 1949 (Box 101, Folder 13)
- Article 14 - Comparisons of Power Cost for Atomic and Conventional Steam Stations, 1949 (Box 101, Folder 14)
- Article 16 - Rejoinder to "The Cowles commision Atomic Cost Estimates: A Reply", 1950 (Box 101, Folder 15)
- Article 17 - The General Theory of Location and Space Economy, 1949 (Box 101, Folder 16)
- Article 19 - Primer of Atom Economics, 1950 (Box 101, Folder 17)
- Article 20 - New England as a Possible Location for an Integrated Iron and Steel Works, 1950 (Box 101, Folder 18)
- Article 21 - Frickey, Burns and Mitchell and the Transport-Building Cycle, 1950 (Box 101, Folder 19)
- Article 22 - Distance Inputs and the Space Economy, 1951 (Box 101, Folder 20)
- Article 23 - Interregional and Regional Input-Outpus Analysis: A Model of a Space-Economy, 1951 (Box 101, Folder 21)
- Article 24 - Atomic Power and Regional Development, 1952 (Box 101, Folder 22)
- Article 25 - A General Location Principle of an Optimum Space Economy, 1952 (Box 101, Folder 23)
- Article 26 - Regional Commodity Balances and Interregional Commodity Flow, 1953 (Box 101, Folder 24)
- Article 27 - Some Remarks on the Marginal Rate of Substitution Between Distance Inputs and Location Theory, 1953 (Box 101, Folder 25)
- Article 28 - Regional Commodity Balances and Interregional Commodity Flows, 1953 (Box 101, Folder 26)
- Article 29 - Some Empirical Results and Problems of Regional Input-Output Analysis, 1953 (Box 101, Folder 27)
- Article 30 - The Economic Base and Structure of the Urban-Metropolitan Region, 1953 (Box 101, Folder 28)
- Article 31 - Some Emerging Concepts and Techniques for Regional Analysis, 1953 (Box 101, Folder 29)
- Article 32 - The Impact of Steel upon the Greater New York-Philadelphia Industrial Region, 1953 (Box 101, Folder 30)